Alan W. Steelman papers, Inclusive: 1960-2003, Bulk: 1973-1976
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislation by Committee, 1973-1976, undated; 7
  - Banking and Currency, 1973-1976; 5
    - Education and Labor, 1973-1976; 3
      - Health (6 of 6), 1973 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Juvenile Delinquency, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - SER/OIC, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Busing, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Education, 1974-1975 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Labor, OSHA, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Right-to-Work, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Busing (1 of 5), 1975 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Busing (2 of 5), 1975 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Busing (3 of 5), 1975 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Busing (4 of 5), 1975 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Busing (5 of 5), 1975 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Child and Family Services, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Education (1 of 5), 1975 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Education (2 of 5), 1975 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Education (3 of 5), 1975 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Education (4 of 5), 1975 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Education (5 of 5), 1975 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Education Veto, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Education, Title IX, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Employment Compensation, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - General, 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Labor, Pensions (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Labor, Pensions (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Labor, Pensions (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Labor, Minimum Wage (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - Labor, Minimum Wage (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Labor, OSHA, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Busing, 1976 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Busing, McDonald’s Bill (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Busing, McDonald’s Bill (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Child and Family Services (1 of 7), 1976 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Child and Family Services (2 of 7), 1976 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Child and Family Services (3 of 7), 1976 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Child and Family Services (4 of 7), 1976 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Child and Family Services (5 of 7), 1976 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Child and Family Services (6 of 7), 1976 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Child and Family Services (7 of 7), 1976 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - General, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Health, 1973; 4
      - General (1 of 4), 1973 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - General (2 of 4), 1973 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - General (3 of 4), 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - General (4 of 4), 1973 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - House Administration, 1974, 1976; 5
      - President Campaign Reform No. 5303, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - President, Office of, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Labor, 1973-1976; 6
      - Common Situs Picketing (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Common Situs Picketing (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Common Situs Picketing (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Common Situs, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - General (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - General (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - General (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - General (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - General (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - General (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - General (1 of 5), 1973 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - General (2 of 5), 1973 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - General (3 of 5), 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - General (4 of 5), 1973 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - General (5 of 5), 1973 (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Labor Per Contract, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Minimum Wage, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - OSHA, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Pensions (1 of 7), 1973 (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Pensions (2 of 7), 1973 (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - Pensions (3 of 7), 1973 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Pensions (4 of 7), 1973 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Pensions (5 of 7), 1973 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Pensions (6 of 7), 1973 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Pensions (7 of 7), 1973 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Public Works, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Right-to-Work, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - Sears Pensions (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Sears Pensions (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Sears Pensions (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - #99, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - #5302, Workmen’s Compensation, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1973-1976; 6
    - Aid, Kissinger and Africa, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Aid, U.N. & Panama Canal (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Aid, U.N. & Panama Canal (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Cambodia and Vietnam Aid (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Cambodia and Vietnam Aid (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Cambodia and Vietnam Aid (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Foreign Affairs (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Foreign Affairs (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Cyprus, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - General, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - General, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - General (1 of 3), 1974 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - General (2 of 3), 1974 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - General (3 of 3), 1974 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Israeli/Arab Conflict, 1975-1976 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Middle East (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Middle East (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Middle East, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Panama Canal, 1975-1976 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Relations (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Relations (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Relations (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Relations, 1973-1974 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Relations (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Relations (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Relations (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Relations (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Relations (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Steelman MidEast Analysis, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Trade, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Turkey, Military Aid (1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Turkey, Military Aid (2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - United Nations (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - United Nations (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - United Nations, 1974 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Vietnam (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Vietnam (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Vietnam (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Vietnam Information, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Government Operations, 1973-1976; 7
    - Consumer Protection Agency (1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Consumer Protection Agency (2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Committee, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Conservation, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Consumer Protection, 1975-1976 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Federal, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Federal, 1974 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - General (1 of 3), 1973-1975 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - General (2 of 3), 1973-1975 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - General (3 of 3), 1973-1975 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - General, 1974-1975 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - General, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Intergovernmental Revenue Sharing, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Privacy, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Revenue Sharing (1 of 6), 1975 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Revenue Sharing (2 of 6), 1975 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Revenue Sharing (3 of 6), 1975 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Revenue Sharing (4 of 6), 1975 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Revenue sharing (5 of 6), 1975 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Revenue Sharing (6 of 6), 1975 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Revenue Sharing Responses (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Revenue Sharing Responses (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Revenue Sharing Letters, 1975-1976 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Revenue Sharing (1 of 5), 1976 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Revenue Sharing (2 of 5), 1976 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Revenue Sharing (3 of 5), 1976 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Revenue Sharing (4 of 5), 1976 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Revenue Sharing (5 of 5), 1976 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs, 1973-1976; 8
    - Topical, 1973-1976; 1
      - Alaska Pipeline, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 7)
      - Boxcar Shortage (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 85, Folder 8)
      - Boxcar Shortage (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Commerce, 1973-1975 (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - Commerce, No Fault, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - Consumer Affairs, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Consumers #119, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - Employee Stock Ownership Plan, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 6)
      - Energy (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Energy (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - General (1 of 5), 1973 (Box 86, Folder 9)
      - General (2 of 5), 1973 (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - General (3 of 5), 1973 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - General (4 of 5), 1973 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - General (5 of 5), 1973 (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - General (1 of 4), 1974 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - General (2 of 4), 1974 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - General (3 of 4), 1974 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - General (4 of 4), 1974 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - General (1 of 6), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 2)
      - General (2 of 6), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 3)
      - General (3 of 6), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - General (4 of 6), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - General (5 of 6), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - General (6 of 6), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 7)
      - General, 1976 (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - Interior lLand Use No.6801-02, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - Interior Land Use (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - Interior Land Use (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - Interior Land Use (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - Interior Land Use (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - Interior Land Use (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Land Use (1 of 5), 1975 (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - Land Use (2 of 5), 1975 (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Land Use (3 of 5), 1975 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - Land Use (4 of 5), 1975 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Land Use (5 of 5), 1975 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - Land Use (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Land Use (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - Land Use, Articles and Editorials, 1972-1975 (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Land Use, General Information (1 of 5), 1973 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Land Use, General Information (2 of 5), 1973 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Land Use, General Information (3 of 5), 1973 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Land Use, General Information (4 of 5), 1973 (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Land Use, General Information (5 of 5), 1973 (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Land Use, Lobbying, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Land Use, Memos, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Land Use Planning Act, HR 10294, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Land Use, Speeches (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Land Use, Speeches (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Land Use, Steelman/Udall, 1975 (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Land and Water Conversation Fund, 1975-1976 (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - National Parks (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - National Parks (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - National security, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Nuclear (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Nuclear (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Nuclear (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Oil Shale, 1973-1975 (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Sales Representative Protection Act, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Save Outdoor America (1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Save Outdoor America (2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Strip Mining (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - Strip Mining (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Surface Mining, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Texas Land Use Report in 8 volumes (1 of 3), 1976 (Box 94a, Folder 1)
      - Texas Land Use Report in 8 volumes (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 94a, Folder 2)
      - Texas Land Use Report in 8 volumes (3 of 3), 1976 (Box 94a, Folder 3)
    - Immigration and Naturalization, 1973-1976; 2
      - General, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - General, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - General, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - General, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Judiciary Committee, 1973-1976; 9
    - Topical, 1973-1976; 1
      - Against Nixon Impeachment (1 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Against Nixon Impeachment (2 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Against Nixon Impeachment (3 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Against Nixon Impeachment (4 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Against Nixon Impeachment (5 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Against Nixon Impeachment (6 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - Against Nixon Impeachment, Pro #117 (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Against Nixon Impeachment, Pro #117 (2 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Against President Impeachment, 1973 May-1974 June (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Anti-Trust Laws, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Busing Bill #5305, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Civil Rights, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Civil Rights, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Civil Rights, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Courts, 1975-1976 (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Courts, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Courts and Crime, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - Courts and Crime (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Courts and Crime (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Courts/Crime, Gun Control (1 of 3), 1976 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Courts/Crime, Gun Control (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Courts/Crime, Gun Control (3 of 3), 1976 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Crime, 1974-1975 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Crime and Criminals, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Crime and Gun Control (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Crime and Gun Control (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Drug Treatment Center, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Drugs, 1974 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Drugs, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Flittie, William, Civil Restraints, 1975 (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - General, 1975-1976 (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Gun Control (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Gun Control (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - Gun Control, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - Gun Control (1 of 6), 1975 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - Gun Control (2 of 6), 1975 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - Gun Control (3 of 6), 1975 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - Gun Control (4 of 6), 1975 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - Gun Control (5 of 6), 1975 (Box 99, Folder 8)
      - Gun Control (6 of 6), 1975 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Hughes, Marie, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Impeachment (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Impeachment (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Impeachment (1 of 3), 1974 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Impeachment (2 of 3), 1974 (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Impeachment (3 of 3), 1974 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - Impeachment Pro/Con (1 of 3), 1974 (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - Impeachment Pro/Con (2 of 3), 1974 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - Impeachment Pro/Con (3 of 3), 1974 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - Impeachment Questionnaires Sent to Steelman, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - Office of the President (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 101, Folder 7)
      - Office of the President (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 101, Folder 8)
      - Polygraph, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 9)
      - President Against Impeachment, 1973-1974 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - President H.R. 11401, 1973 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - President Immunity Impeachment, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - President Immunity Pardon, 1973-1974 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - President Impeachment (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - President Impeachment (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - President Impeachment (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 102, Folder 7)
      - President Impeachment (2 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 102, Folder 8)
      - President Impeachment (1 of 7), 1973 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - President Impeachment (2 of 7), 1973 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - President Impeachment (3 of 7), 1973 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - President Impeachment (4 of 7), 1973 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - President Impeachment (5 of 7), 1973 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - President Impeachment (6 of 7), 1973 (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - President Impeachment (7 of 7), 1973 (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - President Impeachment, 1974 January-February (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - President Impeachment, 1974 July-August (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - Presidential Campaign Reform, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - President-Vice President, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - Prisons, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - Veterans Affairs (1 of 4), 1976 (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - Veterans Affairs (2 of 4), 1976 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - Veterans Affairs (3 of 4), 1976 (Box 104, Folder 8)
      - Veterans Affairs (4 of 4), 1976 (Box 104, Folder 9)
      - Vice President, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 10)
      - Vice President Rockefeller (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 104, Folder 11)
      - Vice President Rockefeller (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Washington Connection Letters, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Watergate, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - Watergate (1 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Watergate (2 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - Watergate (3 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Watergate (4 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - Watergate (5 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - Watergate (6 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - Women’s Rights 86 & 122, 1973-1974 (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - Women's Rights (1 of 3), 1974 (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Women's Rights (2 of 3), 1974 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - Women's Rights (3 of 3), 1974 (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - Women's Rights (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - Women's Rights (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Women's Rights (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 106a, Folder 1)
      - Women's Rights, Abortion, 1976 (Box 106a, Folder 2)
      - Women's Rights, Abortion, 1975 (Box 106a, Folder 3)
      - Women's Rights, ERA, 1976 (Box 106a, Folder 4)
      - Women's Rights, ERA, 1975 (Box 106a, Folder 5)
    - Post Office and Civil Service, 1973-1976; 2
      - General, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - General, 1974 (Box 107, Folder 2)
      - General, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 3)
      - General, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 4)
      - Hatch Act, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 5)
      - Hatch Act, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 6)
      - Pay Raise, 1974 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Science and Astronautics, 1974; 3
      - General (1 of 4), 1974 (Box 107, Folder 8)
      - General (2 of 4), 1974 (Box 108, Folder 1)
      - General (3 of 4), 1974 (Box 108, Folder 2)
      - General (4 of 4), 1974 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Small Business Committee, 1973-1975; 4
      - General, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 4)
      - General (1 of 4), 1974 (Box 108, Folder 5)
      - General (2 of 4), 1974 (Box 108, Folder 6)
      - General (3 of 4), 1974 (Box 108, Folder 7)
      - General (4 of 4), 1974 (Box 108, Folder 8)
      - General (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 108, Folder 9)
      - General (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Ways and Means, 1973-1976; 10
    - Business, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Child Care Deduction, 1973-1974 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Child Support Laws, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Elderly Americans Social Security, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Gasoline Tax, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Health Insurance, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Housing, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Housing, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Industry, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Medicare and Nursing Salary, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Oil Depletion Information, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Professional Standard Review Organization (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Professional Standard Review Organization (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Professional Standards Review Organization (PSRO) information, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - ROBOs, 1976 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Social Security (1 of 5), 1975 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Social Security (2 of 5), 1975 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Social Security (3 of 5), 1975 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Social Security (4 of 5), 1975 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Social Security (5 of 5), 1975 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Social Security, 1976 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Social Security Appeals, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Social Welfare, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Social Welfare (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Social Welfare (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Social Welfare, 1976 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Social Welfare, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Surtax, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Taxes (1 of 4), 1974 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Taxes (2 of 4), 1974 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Taxes (3 of 4), 1974 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Taxes (4 of 4), 1974 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Taxes (1 of 5), 1973 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Taxes (2 of 5), 1973 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Taxes (3 of 5), 1973 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Taxes (4 of 5), 1973 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Taxes (5 of 5), 1973 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Taxes (1 of 5), 1975 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Taxes (2 of 5), 1975 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Taxes (3 of 5), 1975 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Taxes (4 of 5), 1975 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Taxes (5 of 5), 1975 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Taxes (1 of 4), 1976 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Taxes (2 of 4), 1976 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Taxes (3 of 4), 1976 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Taxes (4 of 4), 1976 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Taxes, Charities, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Taxes, Churches, 1974 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Taxes, Energy No. 5311, 1974 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Taxes, Estate, 1975 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Taxes, HVAC Excise, 1975 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Taxes, No. 109, 1974 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Taxes, No. 115, 1974 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Taxes, No. 87, 1974 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Taxes, Public Charities (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Taxes, Public Charities (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Welfare/Food Stamps, 1975 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Cabinet Committee on Spanish-Speaking People, 1973; 11
    - General (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - General (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 115, Folder 11)
- Legislative, 1965-1976, undated; 8
  Three subseriesDL93rd Congress, 94th Congress, and TopicalDLreside in this series. It is the largest in the Steelman papers. These subseries were in binders prior to processing. In the 93rd Congress subseries, many folders center around the economy, Citizens Band radios, ecology, transportation, commerce, and FDA consumer vitamin labeling. Conservation, the EPA, healthcare, transportation, veterans issues, and ecology remain prominent in the 94th Congress series. Unique documents such as materials on urban homesteading and Guam's constitution are in the 93rd and 94th Congresses, respectively. Other interesting pieces comprise a bill brought to the floor of the 93rd Congress to make the marigold the U.S. national flower, and Steelman's baseball cards from his stint in the Congressional Baseball Game. Heavy sampling took place in the 94th Congress subseries. Moreover, a folder in 94th Congress entitled "Patriotism, 'Our United States-Help Save It' " contains a tape recording. A trio of folders on the elderly expound on Steelman's special concern for them, exhibited in photos in the A/V series of the papers. The Topical subseries contains five sub-subseries: General, Amtrak, Big Thicket, Energy, and Trinity River. These five sub-subseries chronicle the areas of expertise (and the largest issues) Steelman worked on during his four years in the U.S. Congress. The Big Thicket and Trinity River sub-subseries demarcate the two large conservation efforts he passed into law at the national level. This series remains in average condition.